Guide to the the Richard W. Lyman, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0215
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Series 1
  - Academic (except Stanford) (Box 159, Folder 263)
  - ACTION, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 264)
  - Far East, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 265)
  - P.R.C./People's Republic of China trip, Nov. 1974 (Box 160, Folder 266)
  - RWL Vacation, 1971 (Box 160, Folder 267)
  - Japan, July 1971 (Box 160, Folder 268)
  - Cambridge, Mass, 8/20-21 1971 (Box 160, Folder 269)
  - England, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 270)
  - Yugoslavia, 1977 (Box 160, Folder 271)
  - Israel, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 272)
  - Russia, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 273)
  - Hong Kong, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 274)
  - Japan, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 275)
  - London, 1978 (Box 160, Folder 276)
  - South Africa, 1978 (Box 160, Folder 277)
  - TIME Leadership Conference (Box 160, Folder 278)
- Chronological Files, Series 2
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1970 August (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1970 October (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1970October (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1970 December (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Congratulatory letters, 1970 Oct.-Nov. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 January (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 February (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 March (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 April (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 May (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 June (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 July (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 August (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 September (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 October (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 November (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1971 December (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 February (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 April (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 May (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 June (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 July (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 August (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 September (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 October (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 November (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1972 December (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 January (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 February (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 March (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 April (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 May (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 June (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 July (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 August (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 September (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 October (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 November (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1973 December (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 January (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 February (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 March (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 April (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 May (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 June (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 July (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 August (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 September (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 October (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 November (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1974 December (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 January (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 February (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 March (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 April (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 May (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 June (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 July (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 August (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 September (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 October (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 November (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1975 December (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 January (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 February (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 March (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 April (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 May (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 June (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 July (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 August (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 September (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 October (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 November (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1976 December (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 January (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 February (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 March (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 April (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 May (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 June (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 July (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 August (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 September (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 October (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 November (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1977 December (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 January (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 February (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 March (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 April (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 May (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 June (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 July (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 August (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 September (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 October (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 November (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Chronological files for President Lyman, 1978 December (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Additional Papers, Series 3
  - Hoover Institute: Board of Overseers, 9/76-12/77; AA4.9.1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 9/76-12/77; AA4.13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fundamental Standard (Honor Code), 1975-76; AD3.10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Speeches RWL's and Others, 9/76-12/77; AD3.22 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Staff Meetings, 1970-72; AD4.11 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Comment Summaries, 1972-77; AD4.20.1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Congratulation Letters, 1977; AD4.20.3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Invitations: Accepted, 11/77-8/78; AD4.20.4.1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Invitations: Declined, 11/77-8/78; AD4.20.4.2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Complaints/Troubled: Mary Gates, AD4.20.5 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Complaints/Troubled: Dee-Dee Jayne Guidera, AD4.20.5 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Complaints/Troubled: Christine Jardetsky, AD4.20.5 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Complaints/Nonsense, 1/78-8/78; AD4.20.5 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Complaints/Nonsense [retrieved], 1976-78; AD4.20.5 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Complaints/Nonsense, 12/76-12/77; AD4.20.5 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Admissions Cases, 1976-78; AD8.1.2 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hoover Institution Board of Overseers, 1972-75; AA4.9.1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Affirmative Action Program (Internal), 9/76-12/77; AD9.6 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Affirmative Action Program (Internal), 9/76-12/77; AD9.6 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Employment Inquiries and Requests, 1978; AD10.1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Grievance Hearings/Cases, AD10.8.10/1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Grievance Hearings/Cases, 9/76-8/78; AD10.8.10/1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Staff Fringe Benefits, 7/74-7/78; AD10.8.9 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Retirement, 9/76-7/78; AD10.8.17 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Tuition Benefit Plan, 3/73-7/78; AD10.8.22 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Commencement, 1977; AD11.7.2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Orientation, 4/76-8/78; AD11.7.7 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Policy: Investment Responsibilities, 4/77-12/77; AD12.7 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Computer Science: Advisory Committee, 1967-72; AD13.10.5/1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Trustee Investment Committee, 1/78-4/78; B14.5 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Trustee Investment Committee, 10/77-12/77; B14.5 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Committees, Commissions, Administration, Panels, etc, 10/75-10/78; C (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Board, 1977-78; C3 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Steering Committees (StC): By Document Number, 2/78-5/78; C4.1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Steering Committees (StC): By Document Number, 9/77-1/78; C4.1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Committees, 6/78-8/78; C4.2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Committees, 1/78-5/78; C4.2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Committees, 1977; C4.2 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Rhodes-Marshall Scholarship Panel (C-AAA-RMP), 7/76-78; C5.1.4 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Libraries, 9/76-12/77; C5.4 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1977-78; C5.7 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation, 11/76-8/78; C6.1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - University Committee on Land and Building Development, 1977-78; C6.6 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Public Events (CPEV), 9/72-8/78; C6.8 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Investment Responsibility, 1977-78; C7.7 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Parking and Transportation, 1/78-8/78; C8.1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Parking and Transportation, 9/76-12/77; C8.1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Federal Legislation, 1976-77; G3.1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1/77-9/77; G3.8 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Educom: Conference (Provost), 7/78; G3.19.12 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Educom:, 6/77-12/77; G3.19.12 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - California State Government, 9/76-77; G7.2 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (CoFHE), 03.1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1977; 03.44 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Pacific Ten Conference, 5/78-10/78; 03.47 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers, 1977; 03.55 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - American Council on Education: Misc, 1977-8/78; 03.8 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Other Universities and Colleges, 10/77-7/78; 08 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - American Association of Universities, 1/78-6/78; 08.7 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - A.A.U.: Council on Federal Relations, 08.7.1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - School of Medicine, 1/78-6/78; PAA4.6 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - School of Medicine, 9/77-12/77; PAA4.6 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Stanford: Miscellany, PAD1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Chicano Affairs, 6/71-8/78; PAD9.2 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Assistant to the President for Chicano Affairs, 10/71-6/78; PAD9.2.1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Sponsored Projects Information Center (SPIC): Evaluation, 1974-75; R1.1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Wonka, Warren G. / Wendy, 6/53-6/67; PAD1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Governor Stanford Locomotive, 5/76-4/77; PAD1.1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Departments, Misc, 9/73-8/76; PAD1.6 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Academic and Administrative Information Projects, 11/73-3/78; PAD1.6.2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Signature Resolutions/Authorizations, 2/74-8/77; PAD1.6.5 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Procedures for Department Heads and Departments, 12/71-12/76; PAD1.6.6 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Recruiting, 11/72-10/78; PAD2.3 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Nepotism, 1/71-11/76; PAD2.18 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - ROTC, 7/73-3/78; PAD2.26 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Higher Education, Misc, 8/76-3/77; PAD2.27 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Guide, 9/72-3/76; PAD3.2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Campus Reports, 3/73-2/77; PAD3.4 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Academic Staff Handbook, 10/75-1/77; PAD3.6 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Handbook, 2/73-8/77; PAD3.7 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Directories: Faculty/Staff/Student, 8/73-9/77; PAD3.8 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fundamental Standard (Honor Code), 9/73-12/77; PAD3.10 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Mailings, ID Mail, 10/69-11/77; PAD3.13 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - University Calendar/Holidays, 8/74-1/78; PAD3.21 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Speeches, RWL's and Others, 9/72-5/77; PAD3.22 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - President's Office, 9/72-5/77; PAD4 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Presidential Powers, 6/72-5/78; PAD4.2 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - President's House, Staff, Car, 8/75-9/76; PAD4.7 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Vice Presidential Group, 5/77-11/77; PAD4.12 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - [title not noted], 3/69-6/76; PAD4.14 (Box 5, Folder 23.1)
  - University Counsel, 1/75-6/78; PAD4.19 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - General, Misc. (Individual Folders, A-Z), 8/69-1/77; PAD4.20 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Condolence Letters/Deceased Lists, 12/75-6/77; PAD4.20.2 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Congratulation Letters, 2/73-7/78; PAD4.20.3 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Invitation, General, 8/74-10/77; PAD4.20.4 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Complaints/Nonsense, 9/73-12/77; PAD4.20.5 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Recommendation letters, 11/71-3/78; PAD4.20.6 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Public Affairs Office, 9/72-10/78; PAD4.22 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Southern California Office, 5/75; PAD4.23 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - New York Office, 2/76-7/76; PAD4.24 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Ombudsman, 5/69-9/77; PAD6 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - [title not noted], 3/76-7/78; PAD7 (Box 6, Folder 4.1)
  - Student Discipline: Inquiries/General Info, 11/74; PAD7.2.3 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - SJC (Stanford Judicial Council) (Cases), 6/70-12/77; PAD7.2.7 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dismissal Cases, 3/77; PAD7.5 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - University Governance, 3/76; PAD7.8 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Admissions Office, 10/75-11/77; PAD8.1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Policy: Admissions/General, 11/72-12/77; PAD8.1.1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Admissions Cases, 4/73-9/76; PAD8.1.2 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Students on Committees, Policy, 3/70-6/76; PAD8.5 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Career Planning & Placement Center, 3/75-11/77; PAD8.7 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 5/74-11/77; PAD8.8 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Student Services & Special Services Office, 5/71-2/78; PAD8.8.2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Policy on Discrimination, 11/71-4/77; PAD8.8.3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Exchange Programs, 2/72-8/76; PAD8.10 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Intern Programs, 8/75-4/78; PAD8.10.2 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies Programs, 9/77-7/78; PAD8.11 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Center in Vienna, 1/73-11/77; PAD8.11.1 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Center in Britain, 2/73-8/77; PAD8.11.2 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Program in Tours, 2/69-2/75; PAD8.11.3 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Stanford Program in Berlin, 4/77-3/78; PAD8.11.4/1 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Stanford Program in Bonn, 1/78-4/78; PAD8.11.4/2 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Center in Italy, 2/73-7/78; PAD8.11.5 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Ad Hoc Commission for Review of Overseas Campuses, 12/72-8/73; PAD8.11.7 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Financial Aids, 9/76-9/78; PAD8.12 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Student Loans, 6/73-11/77; PAD8.12.1 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Graduate Student Financial Aid, 1/74-6/78; PAD8.12.2 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 6/71-6/78; PAD8.18 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Hanna-Honeycomb House, 11/76-6/78; PAD8.18.2 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Lake House, PAD8.18.3 (Box 6, Folder 31.1)
  - Fraternities/Sororities, 2/73-11/77; PAD8.18.8 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Off-Campus Housing, 1/75-4/78; PADS/8.11 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Residence Halls/Staff, 7/72-12/77; PAD8.18.12 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Registrar, 9/77-6/78; PAD8.21 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Registrar, 9/76-12/78; PAD8.21 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Enrollment Data, 9/72-9/78; PAD8.21.1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Minorities, 3/75-7/79; PAD9 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Black Affairs, 1/75-7/78; PAD9.1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Black Student Union (BSU), 9/72-6/78; PAD9.1.2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Native American Indian Affairs, 11/70-3/75; PAD9.3 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action Office, 4/78-7/78; PAD9.6 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action for Women, 10/73-10/77; PAD9.6.3 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Personnel and Employee Relations, 9/76-7/78; PAD10 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Employment Inquiries and Requests, 9/76-3/78; PAD10.1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Policy: Appointment of Lecturers & Other Short-Term Teachers, 12/71-6/78; PAD10.6 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Child Care Program, 5/73-12/77; PAD10.7.5 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - United Stanford Employees, 5/74-8/76; PAD10.7.8 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Personnel Policies/Hiring Practices, 12/74-3/78; PAD10.8 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Collective bargaining, 7/73-2/76; PAD10.8.2 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 2/73-3/77; PAD10.8.3 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Faculty/Staff Fringe Benefits, 10/76-10/77; PAD10.8.9 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Policy: Benefits for Visiting Scholars, Fellows, 5/75-1/76; PAD10.8.9/2 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Grievance Procedures, Faculty/Staff, 1/76-2/78; PAD10.8.10 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Grievance Hearings: Cases, 1/76-7/78; PAD10.8.10/1 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Grievances: Student/Faculty on Academic Matters, 12/76-6/78; PAD10.8.10/3 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Grievances: Van Saun/GSB grievance, 4/77-1/78; PAD10.8.10/3 (Box 7, Folder 20.1)
  - Long Term Disability, 6/72-1/78; PAD10.8.14/5 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Leaves of Absence "Absences" etc, 9/69-12/78; PAD10.8.15 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Retirement, 9/77-7/78; PAD10.8.17 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Early Retirement, 5/72-3/78; PAD10.8.17/1 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Retirement Legislation, 7/77-6/78; PAD10.8.17/2 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Salaries: Other Institutions, 9/72-4/77; PAD10.8.19/1 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Policy: Travel, 1/73-10/77; PAD10.8.21 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Tuition Benefit Plan, 12/75-2/78; PAD10.8.22 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - University Services, Misc, 12/72-11/76; PAD11 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Service Operations, 2/73-5/78; PAD11.4 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Energy, Info / Misc, 1/74-12/78; PAD11.4.2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Police Services/Campus Security, 12/72-9/77; PAD11.6 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 2/75-6/77; PAD11.7.2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dedications, 5/74-1/77; PAD11.7.4 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Founders' Day, 3/72-2/75; PAD11.7.6 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Orientation, 8/74-11/77; PAD11.7.7 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Baccalaureate, 4/77; PAD11.7.15 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Publications Service/Communications, 8/73-7/76; PAD11.8 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Copyright Policy, 10/76-1/78; PAD11.8.1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Records, Privacy of, 10/72-6/78; PAD11.8.3 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Stanford News Service, 9/72-5/77; PAD11.8.4 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - News Service Reports/Releases, 5/73-10/77; PAD11.8.5 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Press, 3/73-1/78; PAD11.8.9 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Surveys, Studies & Questionnaires, 11/71-5/78; PAD11.8.10 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Publications, Misc, 2/76-4/78; PAD11.8.11 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Facts, 12/75; PAD11.8.11/1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Television Instructional Network, 5/76-1/78; PAD11.8.13 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Financing Higher Education/Higher Education Acts, 2/74-5/76; PAD12.1 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Business and Finance, 7/78-8/78; PAD12.2 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Budgets, 11/76-12/78; PAD12.5 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Room and Board Rates, 5/74-11/77; PAD12.5.3 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Tuition, 10/76-4/78; PAD12.5.4 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Wage and Price Freeze Issue, 10/72-7/73; PAD12.5.5 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Financial Reports, 10/74-12/7; PAD12.6 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Policy: Investment Responsibilities, 5/75-10/77; PAD12.7 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Consulting Policy/Conflict of Interest, 11/77-8/78; PAD12.7.1 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Health & Safety, 8/73-2/78; PAD12.8.1 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Taxes: Tax Reform, 9/73-8/78; PAD12.9 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Vice President for Development, 1/73-8/78; PAD12.10 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Office of Development, 1/75-11/78; PAD12.10.1 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Endowment: Stanford, 12/67-12/77; PAD12.10.2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fund Raising/Filer Committee, 5/76-6/78; PAD12.10.3 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Estates & Wills, 11/73-8/78; PAD12.10.3/3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Annual Fund (Inner Quad), 2/76-12/77; PAD12.10.3/4 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Gift Policies: Gift Summaries, 2/75-8/78; PAD12.10.3/5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Gifts, (Permanent File) Misc, 1/75-8/78; PAD12.10.3/5-1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - American Cancer Society, 9/76-6/77; PAD12.10.3/5-2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Standard Oil of California, 5/74-8/78; PAD12.10.3/5-5 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Bechtel Corporation, 1/75-7/75; PAD12.10.3/5-7 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Foundation of New York, 10/73-6/77; PAD12.10.3/5-10 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Criley, C. A, 11/77-2/78; PAD12.10.3/5-12 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Crocker, Mrs. Roy P, 10/77-3/78; PAD12.10.3/5-13 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Crown, John H. and Family, 7/78; PAD12.10.3/5-14 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Dickenson, Fairleigh S., Jr, 3/73-8/78; PAD12.10.3/5-17 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Ely, Northcutt, 8/76; PAD12.10.3/5-21 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Gates Foundation, 8/73-12/78; PAD12.10.3/5-24.5 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - General Motors Corporation, Scholarship Fellowships, General Gifts, 4/75-4/78; PAD12.10.3/5-25 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Glenmede Trust Company, 8/74-1/78; PAD12.10.3/5-26 (Box 9, Folder 17)